TEGAR MUHAMAD HAFIEZ

083872584941 https://www.linkedin.com/in/tegarmhafiez/

Jakarta, Indonesia

Bachelor of Computer Science who has an interest in programming, understand systems, application, and web development. As well as database management, skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python and PHP programming languages. Experience troubleshooting software and hardware as well as the capability of understanding IT Quality Assurance for manual and automation testing.

EDUCATION

Sekolah Tinggi Ilmu Komputer Cipta Karya Informatika - Jakarta Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science – Informatic Technology 3.40/4.00

2018 - 2022

WORK EXPERIENCE

Save The Children Indonesia

(Jan 2021 - Des 2021)

Local Facilitator

As an agent to handle and also supervise the division goals. In terms of handling of football division, I teach and report every event that is related to the division's goals.

PT.Indokomas Buana Perkasa

(Mar 2023 - Sept 2023)

Technical Administrator

Part of Commissioning Division on Data Center project in Karawang - Indonesia.

- As commissioning admin, update and report are part of my duties. Based on the actual inspection from other parties, I need to make and update the report in the client platform to make sure the data deliver correctly and easy to understand to all parties.
- Setting, running and basic repairing site office inventory (printer, scanner, laptop and some technical equipment).

SKILL

Soft Skill: Problem Solving, Teamwork, Communication, Organization

Hard Skill: Programming Language (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, PHP) Framework (Laravel 9), can make a test case, manual/automation testing, fundamental Microsoft Azure.

Course: Procore Administrator (Procore Technologies), Front End Web Development (Coding Studio)

Basic Python (Udemy), Microsoft Azure Data Fundamental (Microsoft X Prakerja), Quality Assurance Class (HabisKerja.com)

Portofolio: https://github.com/HAFIEZ-TEGAR/Portofolio